const QuestionBank = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "1. If a triangle has angles 135°, 15°, 30°. Is it an obtuse triangle?",
    answer: "yes",
    options: ["yes", "no"],
    bgColor: "aqua"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "2. If a triangle has angles 115°, 25°, 40°. Is it an acute triangle?",
    answer: "no",
    options: ["yes", "no"],
    bgColor: "aqua"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "3. If a triangle has angles 900, 600, 300. Is it a right angle triangle?",
    answer: "yes",
    options: ["yes", "no"],
    bgColor: "aqua"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "4. A triangle has angles 600, 600, 600. Is it an equilateral triangle?",
    answer: "yes",
    options: ["yes", "no"],
    bgColor: "aqua"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "5. If a triangle has angles 250, 750, 800. Is it an acute triangle?",
    answer: "yes",
    options: ["yes", "no"],
    bgColor: "aqua"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "6. If a triangle has 2 sides with equal lengths and 750 angle between them. What is the type of triangle?",
    answer: "Isosceles",
    options: ["Equilateral", "Isosceles", "Right Angle traingle"],
    bgColor: "aqua"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "7. If a triangle has 2 angles of 750. What is the measure of third angle in degree?",
    answer: "30",
    options: ["25", "30", "15"],
    bgColor: "aqua"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "8. If a triangle has 2 sides with equal lengths and 600 angle between them. What is the type of triangle?",
    answer: "Both",
    options: ["Equilateral", "Isosceles", "Both"],
    bgColor: "aqua"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "9. The perimeter of an equilateral triangle is 15cm. What is the length of one side?",
    answer: "5cm",
    options: ["15cm", "45cm", "5cm"],
    bgColor: "aqua"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "10. If a triangle has sides of 2cm, 3cm, 4cm, what is the type of triangle?",
    answer: "Scalene",
    options: ["Equilateral", "Isosceles", "Scalene"],
    bgColor: "aqua"
  }
];

export default QuestionBank;
